



# **Martin Bosák**

**Date of birth:** 23/05/1995 | **Nationality:** Czech | **Gender:** Male | **Phone number:** 

(+420) 723694379 (Mobile) | **Email address:** <u>bosamar@seznam.cz</u>

### ABOUT ME

I am 29 years old teacher from Czech Republic.

To be completely honest I do not have any experience working in any accountant or corporate position. However I am interested in finance, so I constantly educate myself. I have my own portfolio, do my own taxes and generaly try to improve my knowledge in this field. Also I consider myself as very hardworking person and quick lerner.

I worked as a marketing manager in floorball club, where I was dealing with financial planning and budgets. Also I founded there a new e-shop, that I also managed for some time. That involved working with invoices and dealing with taxes.

When I was younger, I also went through many trainings in Partners (company of financial advisors). In the end I did not work there, but it was very helpful for my financial literacy.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

01/09/2021 - CURRENT Prague, Czechia

**ENGLISH TEACHER ZŠ KBELY** 

01/07/2021 - 01/06/2022 Prague, Czechia

E-SHOP MANAGER BLACK ANGELS

15/12/2020 - 01/06/2022 Prague, Czechia

**MARKETING MANAGER BLACK ANGELS** 

19/12/2019 - 01/06/2020 Prague, Czechia

**DATA ANALYST LIVESPORT** 

17/10/2015 - 16/12/2018 Prague

**TOURIST INFORMATION + TICKET SALESPERSON PRAGUE CASTLE** 

19/12/2014 - 19/02/2015 Praha, Czechia

**CASHIER BURGER KING** 

10/06/2013 - 10/08/2013 Zdiby, Czechia

**WAITER CAFE ZDIBY** 

#### EDUCATION AND TRAINING

01/10/2014 - 25/05/2017 Prague, Czechia

CHARLES UNIVERSITY, FACULTY OF PHILOSOPHY AND ARTS - MONGOLIAN STUDIES Charles University

2010 - 2014

**GRAMMAR SCHOOL** Českolipská

## LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **CZECH LANGUAGE** 

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	
ENGLISH	C2	C2	C2	C2	C2
GERMAN	B1	B1	B1	B1	В1
MONGOLIAN	A2	B1	B1	B1	A2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user